(Police Sirens)
You were made to be ruled
(cars exploding)
(military men aiming their guns followed by a military jeep with rubble surrounding them)
In the end,
it'll be every man for himself
(cars exploding)
(helicopter whirring)
What do we do?
(Dramatic rock music playing in the background)
We get ready.
There was an idea
to bring together
a group of remarkable people.
So when we needed them,
they could fight the battles
that we never could.
Gentleman,
What are you prepared to do?
No offence but I don't play well with others
Big man in a suit of armour. Take that away, what are you?
A genius, billionaire, playboy, philanthropist
(Laughing)
(rock music playing)
If we can't protect the earth,
you can be damn sure we'll avenge it.
(Ironman flies across the city)
Doctor Banner, your work in unparralelled
And I'm a huge fan of the way you lose control and turn into an enormous green rage monster
Thanks.