The fate of the universe lies on your shoulders
Now whatever you do,
Don't push this button.
Because that will set off the bomb immediately and we'll all be dead.
(gasps)
Now repeat back what I just said
I am groot
No! No that's the button that will kill everyone! Try again.
I am groot.
Uh huh
I am groot
I am groot!
NO!
(rock music playing)
Showtime a-holes!
(screams)
(explosion and people falling)
(Peter flying a spaceship and shooting at other spaceships, exploding them)
Screw you, spaceship!
(groot screaming)
Does anybody have some tape out there? I wanna put some tape over the death button.
Nobody has any tape.
Not a single person has tape?
You have an atomic bomb in your bag if anybody's going to have tape it's you!
I have to do everything!
You're wasting a lot of time with groot!
I am Groot!
That's a really bad sign.
(rock music playing)
(explosions, gun shots)
If I touch someone, I can feel their feelings. You feel.. love.
Yeah, I guess yeah, I feel a general, unselfish love for..
No. Sexual love.
No. No I don't.
For her! (pointing at Gamora)
No!
(Drax laughing)
She just told everyone your deepest darkest secret!
Dude! Come on I think you are over reacting a little bit.
(still laughing, now pointing) you must be so embarrassed!
Do me, do me, do me!
(music playing)